// Generated by Framer (a96673f)
import{jsx as _jsx,jsxs as _jsxs}from"react/jsx-runtime";import{addFonts,addPropertyControls,ControlType,cx,getFonts,useConstant,useIsOnFramerCanvas,useLocaleInfo,useVariantState,withCSS}from"framer";import{LayoutGroup,motion,MotionConfigContext}from"framer-motion";import*as React from"react";import RowCopy7 from"https://framerusercontent.com/modules/6LoIa7J6IjAO6gxNg5qm/saWMiMVENCye5xYqDYFi/aNTTOZgJK.js";import RowCopy2 from"https://framerusercontent.com/modules/rUJdRsC9S9v3SXWyJTSc/GZYMGiJ52QLQTFDTmtre/Bqo2raSqs.js";import RowCopy4 from"https://framerusercontent.com/modules/oqVR3NXLw0GF2IPT6Uwy/Xpi2zL59lD23LdmsUpjk/GdQvVw9ox.js";import Row from"https://framerusercontent.com/modules/8m1e5MfCeszV3tJNt5vq/GJeDJlbFLi1sMybcjEzY/IQIoI4vG2.js";import RowCopy3 from"https://framerusercontent.com/modules/9mlGvonmxj0YabiSyeun/NWDmfb5cOvofknt56Q9h/JUImlAs3g.js";import RowCopy from"https://framerusercontent.com/modules/hYaZr83thBYB4jXDSIMx/gcZEOBSlyz3dFqWsqx53/LRYn7VIJ1.js";import RowCopy5 from"https://framerusercontent.com/modules/fqtCWBM4fnSUAwnVVBcd/IsVCR1lRikTD7Mku9t2U/rkbVRl02q.js";import RowCopy6 from"https://framerusercontent.com/modules/g06G9AqWnn9ezMiPgK4A/Nw1kHHvRjYsVtKlarG1w/taF93TAUG.js";const RowFonts=getFonts(Row);const RowCopyFonts=getFonts(RowCopy);const RowCopy2Fonts=getFonts(RowCopy2);const RowCopy3Fonts=getFonts(RowCopy3);const RowCopy4Fonts=getFonts(RowCopy4);const RowCopy5Fonts=getFonts(RowCopy5);const RowCopy6Fonts=getFonts(RowCopy6);const RowCopy7Fonts=getFonts(RowCopy7);const cycleOrder=["glb3BNyY_","VjmyaXKyA"];const serializationHash="framer-0zGrp";const variantClassNames={glb3BNyY_:"framer-v-hea18f",VjmyaXKyA:"framer-v-xm23p2"};function addPropertyOverrides(overrides,...variants){const nextOverrides={};variants===null||variants===void 0?void 0:variants.forEach(variant=>variant&&Object.assign(nextOverrides,overrides[variant]));return nextOverrides;}const transitions={default:{damping:40,delay:0,mass:1,stiffness:400,type:"spring"}};const Transition=({value,children})=>{const config=React.useContext(MotionConfigContext);const transition=value!==null&&value!==void 0?value:config.transition;const contextValue=React.useMemo(()=>({...config,transition}),[JSON.stringify(transition)]);return /*#__PURE__*/_jsx(MotionConfigContext.Provider,{value:contextValue,children:children});};const humanReadableVariantMap={"Variant 2":"VjmyaXKyA",Homepage:"glb3BNyY_"};const getProps=({height,id,width,...props})=>{var _humanReadableVariantMap_props_variant,_ref;return{...props,variant:(_ref=(_humanReadableVariantMap_props_variant=humanReadableVariantMap[props.variant])!==null&&_humanReadableVariantMap_props_variant!==void 0?_humanReadableVariantMap_props_variant:props.variant)!==null&&_ref!==void 0?_ref:"glb3BNyY_"};};const createLayoutDependency=(props,variants)=>variants.join("-")+props.layoutDependency;const Component=/*#__PURE__*/React.forwardRef(function(props,ref){const{activeLocale,setLocale}=useLocaleInfo();const{style,className,layoutId,variant,...restProps}=getProps(props);const{baseVariant,classNames,gestureVariant,setGestureState,setVariant,transition,variants}=useVariantState({cycleOrder,defaultVariant:"glb3BNyY_",transitions,variant,variantClassNames});const layoutDependency=createLayoutDependency(props,variants);const isOnCanvas=useIsOnFramerCanvas();const initialVariant=useConstant(()=>variant);const ref1=React.useRef(null);const defaultLayoutId=React.useId();const sharedStyleClassNames=[];return /*#__PURE__*/_jsx(LayoutGroup,{id:layoutId!==null&&layoutId!==void 0?layoutId:defaultLayoutId,children:/*#__PURE__*/_jsx(Transition,{value:transition,children:/*#__PURE__*/_jsxs(motion.div,{...restProps,animate:variants,className:cx(serializationHash,...sharedStyleClassNames,"framer-hea18f",className,classNames),"data-framer-name":"Homepage",initial:isOnCanvas?variant:initialVariant,layoutDependency:layoutDependency,layoutId:"glb3BNyY_",onHoverEnd:()=>setGestureState({isHovered:false}),onHoverStart:()=>setGestureState({isHovered:true}),onTap:()=>setGestureState({isPressed:false}),onTapCancel:()=>setGestureState({isPressed:false}),onTapStart:()=>setGestureState({isPressed:true}),ref:ref!==null&&ref!==void 0?ref:ref1,style:{backgroundColor:"rgb(18, 24, 33)",borderBottomLeftRadius:20,borderBottomRightRadius:20,borderTopLeftRadius:20,borderTopRightRadius:20,...style},...addPropertyOverrides({VjmyaXKyA:{"data-framer-name":"Variant 2"}},baseVariant,gestureVariant),children:[/*#__PURE__*/_jsx(motion.div,{className:"framer-8sa76y-container",layoutDependency:layoutDependency,layoutId:"B02x7k4rz-container",children:/*#__PURE__*/_jsx(Row,{answer:"It all boils down to how much skin you’re willing to put in the game with The Real World.\n\nYet, it's worth noting that a hefty number of our students have successfully recouped their investment in just a matter of weeks.",height:"100%",id:"B02x7k4rz",layoutId:"B02x7k4rz",question:"How soon can I expect to see returns on my investment?",style:{width:"100%"},variant:"TvPlYF8uL",width:"100%",...addPropertyOverrides({VjmyaXKyA:{answer:"A cellphone or computer to access our app.",question:"What do you need to get started?"}},baseVariant,gestureVariant)})}),/*#__PURE__*/_jsx(motion.div,{className:"framer-195tmer","data-framer-name":"Line",layoutDependency:layoutDependency,layoutId:"kWO8QooR5",style:{backgroundColor:"rgba(0, 0, 0, 0.05)"}}),/*#__PURE__*/_jsx(motion.div,{className:"framer-tpqhw0-container",layoutDependency:layoutDependency,layoutId:"OcuxTRkET-container",children:/*#__PURE__*/_jsx(RowCopy,{answer:"Not at all.\n\nIn The Real World, our curriculum includes contemporary strategies for wealth generation like copywriting and freelancing, which you can embark on without any initial investment.",height:"100%",id:"OcuxTRkET",layoutId:"OcuxTRkET",question:"Will I require additional funds after joining The Real World?",style:{width:"100%"},variant:"peyhYzP8I",width:"100%",...addPropertyOverrides({VjmyaXKyA:{answer:"- You will be given access to your own account within our mobile/computer app. Everything you need is inside of there. NO this is not some telegram chat. You will have an app you can access.",question:"Where do I access the information and calls"}},baseVariant,gestureVariant)})}),/*#__PURE__*/_jsx(motion.div,{className:"framer-h623pk","data-framer-name":"Line",layoutDependency:layoutDependency,layoutId:"Ta5UFd6RC",style:{backgroundColor:"rgba(0, 0, 0, 0.05)"}}),/*#__PURE__*/_jsx(motion.div,{className:"framer-q0xulc-container",layoutDependency:layoutDependency,layoutId:"e_OleauyV-container",children:/*#__PURE__*/_jsx(RowCopy2,{answer:"Absolutely, you have the freedom to cancel your membership at your discretion.\n\nNonetheless, it's worth noting that a significant number of The Real World students opt to continue their membership, having earned sufficient funds to cover their upcoming month's fees, and often even more.",height:"100%",id:"e_OleauyV",layoutId:"e_OleauyV",question:"Is it possible to terminate my membership at any given time?",style:{width:"100%"},variant:"IcuDJ3E8H",width:"100%",...addPropertyOverrides({VjmyaXKyA:{answer:"- Age isn't a limiting factor to success. I've had students as young as 14 making upwards of $6k. All the way to salarymen coming in and replacing their jobs.",question:"Does Your Age Limit Your Success Rate?"}},baseVariant,gestureVariant)})}),/*#__PURE__*/_jsx(motion.div,{className:"framer-1sscqie-container",layoutDependency:layoutDependency,layoutId:"Nk8Q99m4E-container",children:/*#__PURE__*/_jsx(RowCopy3,{answer:"Absolutely not, although we do advise individuals below 18 to talk it over with a parent or guardian prior to enrolling in The Real World.\n\nRather than spending on the latest video games that lose their charm in no time, you have the chance to become part of our community, kickstart your own venture, and leave your friends and family in awe as you elevate your life in tangible ways.",height:"100%",id:"Nk8Q99m4E",layoutId:"Nk8Q99m4E",question:"Is there any age restriction for joining?",style:{width:"100%"},variant:"kUSnHPSUK",width:"100%",...addPropertyOverrides({VjmyaXKyA:{answer:"- Within your first week you will make progress towards picking a highly profitable skill and begin putting together an offer. Realistically within 30 to 90 days you will be making money if you complete your daily checklist.",question:"How long until I make progress?"}},baseVariant,gestureVariant)})}),/*#__PURE__*/_jsx(motion.div,{className:"framer-fe2e2k-container",layoutDependency:layoutDependency,layoutId:"ZMhIlSqgw-container",children:/*#__PURE__*/_jsx(RowCopy4,{answer:"Absolutely not.\n\nRemember, this is a mentorship program, designed for learning and growth.\n\nSimply adhere to our comprehensive lessons and expert advice, and you'll be on your way to establishing a lucrative venture.",height:"100%",id:"ZMhIlSqgw",layoutId:"ZMhIlSqgw",question:"I have no prior knowledge of the skills you provide instruction on. Will this hinder my progress?",style:{width:"100%"},variant:"nBgB0lFiM",width:"100%",...addPropertyOverrides({VjmyaXKyA:{answer:"- As with anything in life, you get out of this what you put in. Some of our students only dedicate 30 minutes a day. Others dedicate 2 hours a day. What's most important is you make time DAILY to complete your checklists and action steps.",question:"How many hours a day does this require?"}},baseVariant,gestureVariant)})}),/*#__PURE__*/_jsx(motion.div,{className:"framer-ekqygs-container",layoutDependency:layoutDependency,layoutId:"oLVqaJaSn-container",children:/*#__PURE__*/_jsx(RowCopy5,{answer:"The guiding principle of The Real World is expediency.\n\nThe strategies we impart are crafted for swift implementation.\n\nTherefore, dedicating just 30 minutes daily to absorb teachings from your mentors and put them into practice is sufficient.",height:"100%",id:"oLVqaJaSn",layoutId:"oLVqaJaSn",question:"I'm quite pressed for time; is it still feasible for me to participate?",style:{width:"100%"},variant:"RWst7q5FP",width:"100%",...addPropertyOverrides({VjmyaXKyA:{answer:"- This isn't one of those programs where someone makes a few thousand dollars doing something and then decides to launch a coaching program. Every professor (myself included) has dedicated years to building their own business. We are still running our own businesses to stay up to date on the ever changing business landscape. ",question:"What makes you different from other programs/teachers?"}},baseVariant,gestureVariant)})}),/*#__PURE__*/_jsx(motion.div,{className:"framer-1nn4qbl-container",layoutDependency:layoutDependency,layoutId:"tHPCgbhJ5-container",children:/*#__PURE__*/_jsx(RowCopy6,{answer:"Absolutely not.\n\nThe Real World specializes in online wealth-building strategies, making your location irrelevant to your potential success.",height:"100%",id:"tHPCgbhJ5",layoutId:"tHPCgbhJ5",question:"I reside in X country; will that pose any issues?",style:{width:"100%"},variant:"v3SJ14rwZ",width:"100%",...addPropertyOverrides({VjmyaXKyA:{answer:"- I post daily to Twitter (now X) on @moneybaglives and on Instagram @realdylanmadden. You can see the content and an inside look at who I am.",question:"How can I find out more about you?"}},baseVariant,gestureVariant)})}),/*#__PURE__*/_jsx(motion.div,{className:"framer-1o4qe5m-container",layoutDependency:layoutDependency,layoutId:"io_Blh1bx-container",children:/*#__PURE__*/_jsx(RowCopy7,{answer:"Hustler’s University represented the initial phase of our 3-Step Plan, emerging as a flourishing money-making community with 150,000 students amidst The Matrix’s influences.\n\n‍Transitioning to Step 2, we introduce The Real World.\n\nIn this phase, we possess our dedicated payment systems, servers, and banking connections, free from the constraints of Matrix-controlled frameworks. This autonomy allows us to unveil previously undisclosed wealth-building strategies, elevating your financial journey beyond what was possible at Hustler’s University.",height:"100%",id:"io_Blh1bx",layoutId:"io_Blh1bx",question:"Is there a difference between Hustler’s University and The Real World?",style:{width:"100%"},variant:"w8WHS8HNk",width:"100%",...addPropertyOverrides({VjmyaXKyA:{answer:"- You are learning how to operate a freelancing business from me. Meaning you will offer services such as AI, copywriting, video editing, web design, and more.\n\nWhile also having access (included in this package) to other professors who reach Ecom, Business Mastery, Content Creation, AI Mastery, Crypto, and more.",question:"This sounds good, but what exactly am I learning?"}},baseVariant,gestureVariant)})})]})})});});const css=['.framer-0zGrp[data-border="true"]::after, .framer-0zGrp [data-border="true"]::after { content: ""; border-width: var(--border-top-width, 0) var(--border-right-width, 0) var(--border-bottom-width, 0) var(--border-left-width, 0); border-color: var(--border-color, none); border-style: var(--border-style, none); width: 100%; height: 100%; position: absolute; box-sizing: border-box; left: 0; top: 0; border-radius: inherit; pointer-events: none; }',"@supports (aspect-ratio: 1) { body { --framer-aspect-ratio-supported: auto; } }",".framer-0zGrp.framer-1te66g5, .framer-0zGrp .framer-1te66g5 { display: block; }",".framer-0zGrp.framer-hea18f { align-content: center; align-items: center; display: flex; flex-direction: column; flex-wrap: nowrap; gap: 0px; height: min-content; justify-content: center; overflow: hidden; padding: 0px 20px 0px 20px; position: relative; width: 1000px; will-change: var(--framer-will-change-override, transform); }",".framer-0zGrp .framer-8sa76y-container, .framer-0zGrp .framer-tpqhw0-container, .framer-0zGrp .framer-q0xulc-container, .framer-0zGrp .framer-1sscqie-container, .framer-0zGrp .framer-fe2e2k-container, .framer-0zGrp .framer-ekqygs-container, .framer-0zGrp .framer-1nn4qbl-container, .framer-0zGrp .framer-1o4qe5m-container { flex: none; height: auto; position: relative; width: 100%; }",".framer-0zGrp .framer-195tmer, .framer-0zGrp .framer-h623pk { flex: none; height: 1px; overflow: hidden; position: relative; width: 100%; }","@supports (background: -webkit-named-image(i)) and (not (font-palette:dark)) { .framer-0zGrp.framer-hea18f { gap: 0px; } .framer-0zGrp.framer-hea18f > * { margin: 0px; margin-bottom: calc(0px / 2); margin-top: calc(0px / 2); } .framer-0zGrp.framer-hea18f > :first-child { margin-top: 0px; } .framer-0zGrp.framer-hea18f > :last-child { margin-bottom: 0px; } }"];/**
 * This is a generated Framer component.
 * @framerIntrinsicHeight 630
 * @framerIntrinsicWidth 1000
 * @framerCanvasComponentVariantDetails {"propertyName":"variant","data":{"default":{"layout":["fixed","auto"]},"VjmyaXKyA":{"layout":["fixed","auto"]}}}
 * @framerImmutableVariables true
 * @framerDisplayContentsDiv false
 */const Framerdrcs4Sl26=withCSS(Component,css,"framer-0zGrp");export default Framerdrcs4Sl26;Framerdrcs4Sl26.displayName="Accordion";Framerdrcs4Sl26.defaultProps={height:630,width:1e3};addPropertyControls(Framerdrcs4Sl26,{variant:{options:["glb3BNyY_","VjmyaXKyA"],optionTitles:["Homepage","Variant 2"],title:"Variant",type:ControlType.Enum}});addFonts(Framerdrcs4Sl26,[...RowFonts,...RowCopyFonts,...RowCopy2Fonts,...RowCopy3Fonts,...RowCopy4Fonts,...RowCopy5Fonts,...RowCopy6Fonts,...RowCopy7Fonts]);
export const __FramerMetadata__ = {"exports":{"Props":{"type":"tsType","annotations":{"framerContractVersion":"1"}},"default":{"type":"reactComponent","name":"Framerdrcs4Sl26","slots":[],"annotations":{"framerIntrinsicWidth":"1000","framerDisplayContentsDiv":"false","framerCanvasComponentVariantDetails":"{\"propertyName\":\"variant\",\"data\":{\"default\":{\"layout\":[\"fixed\",\"auto\"]},\"VjmyaXKyA\":{\"layout\":[\"fixed\",\"auto\"]}}}","framerImmutableVariables":"true","framerIntrinsicHeight":"630","framerContractVersion":"1"}},"__FramerMetadata__":{"type":"variable"}}}
//# sourceMappingURL=./drcs4Sl26.map